const quiz3data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "James ___ have asked me before he took my phone.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "should", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "would", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'should + have + past participle' to talk about an obligation in the past. We often indicate some criticism or regret."
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "It's six o'clock. The bus ___ have arrived by now.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "might", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "should", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'may have' and 'might have' to make guesses about the past."
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "I ___ have called you, but I didn't know your number.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "could", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "would", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use 'would + have + past participle' to show that you wanted to do something in the past, but you could not."
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "His english ___ have improved by the time the exam comes round.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "should", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "may", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use 'may/might + have + past participle' to say that by some time in the future, it is possible that something will have happened."
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "Sally ___ have gone to Oxford University, but she decided to travel instead.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "would", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "could", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use 'could + have + past participle' to say that something was possible in the past, but it didn't happen."
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "If the train was on time, I ___ have arrived in London early this evening.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "should", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "would", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'should + have + past participle' to talk about an expectation that something happened, has happened, or will happen."
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "I was so worried about you. You ___ called!",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "might", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "should", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use 'should + have + past participle' to say that something didn't happen, but we wish it had happened."
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "My grandmother ___ have disapproved this exhibition.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "should", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "would", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use 'would + have + past participle' when we want to indicate that we think an unreal past situation is certain."
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "The profits of the company ___ well reach Â£100 million this year.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "should", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "might", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use 'may well, might well or could well' to say it is likely that something will happen."
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "The passengers on the bus ___ have been extremely frightened.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "should", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "must", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use 'must + have + past participle' to express a conclusion about something that happened in the past. "
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "Jane is not here. She ___ have forgotten about the meeting.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "might", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "should", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'may/might/could + have + past participle' to say it is possible that something happened in the past."
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "The car driver ___ have tried to pass between two buses.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "would", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "might", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use 'might + have + past participle' to express an opinion: an uncertain guess, a speculation, based on very little information."
    },
  ]
export default quiz3data
